(THIS SERIES IS AN ADULT ANIMATION
INTENDED FOR VIEWERS)
(WHO ARE OF LEGAL AGE
ACCORDING TO LOCAL LAWS AND REGULATIONS.)
(THIS STORY IS PURELY FICTIONAL AND BEARS
NO RELATION TO REAL PEOPLE, ORGANIZATIONS, OR EVENTS.)
(ALL CHARACTERS ARE OF LEGAL AGE OF CONSENT.)
(THE TITLE MAY CONTAIN SENSITIVE CONTENT
SUCH AS SEXUAL OR VIOLENT SCENES. DO NOT IMITATE.)
ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS, PLACES,
LAWS AND NAMES ARE PURELY FICTIONAL.
PLEASE BE AWARE THAT THE WORK
CONTAINS SOME EXTREME LANGUAGE.
Get pregnant, now!
W-Who's this old guy?
TOSHIAKI NIURA
ADVOCATE FOR FREE LEWDNESS
That's Governor Aloha-sama.
The one who graciously
created the Perverted Ordinance.
He's the messiah of Seiran Island.
No, he's the "Fuckssiah."
The Fuckssiaaaaaah!!
I'm going to crush the Perverted Ordinance!
NUKITASHI THE ANIMATION
Just the failed creations
of the ones before
Some rebel elements, rotten to the core
Beyond the wire fence,
a world of sleek design
I stared it down,
a secret that was only mine
Inside the perfect world
that someone else designed
If we were different,
we were always left behind
In a gentle world for everyone to behold
Someone untold cried in agony
Just a laughing mob,
a mindless flock of crows,
Always saying "NO"
to things that nobody knows
With values and with normalcy they pose
Armed with all their theories, I suppose
And then they call us useless pros
Even if you know
that you are in the wrong
Remember what it means
to live your life and to be strong
If you truly wish
you could change today right now
With that very heart,
go on and show them
Don't you hesitate, don't ever stop
Destroy it, make the whole world drop
With all that passion,
pierce right through it all
Go anywhere you want
Can't even love yourself?
For the impatience or the mess you've made
Because right here and now,
we're standing tall
We are alive and breathing after all
Line up.
Open your bags immediately.
What?
At a time like this?
Hey, you.
Is that...
She is fine.
Huh?
Next.
You with the glasses, step forward.
Huh? I'm...
Haaah.
I wasn't noticed again.
Huh?
Are you the transfer student...
from the "virgin" incident
that was reported?
My guys said they let a virgin get away.
You did get to fucked probably
after that, right?
Yes, we've been
fucking nonstop since then.
Then that's fine.
Show me your bag.
Textbooks, a pencil case, a tablet, and...
Huh?
This is...
An egg.
An egg?
What is it for?
Masturbation.
What? Masturbation?!
If you're having sex with someone,
you shouldn't need that.
But it's compact, easy to use,
and can even be used...
as interior decoration.
It's a really popular product.
Don't tell me you're so engrossed
in masturbation that you're neglecting sex.
O-Of course not.
The previous incident
was also your fault.
Ah! Sorry.
You washed and brought it for me?
Yeah, if we're gonna do creampie play,
this is the only choice.
E-Exactly.
I lost yesterday,
but today I'm gonna cum a lot more!
Hmm.
If the model fucking XXX
Katagiri is using it,
it must be an incredibly perverted item.
Permission granted. Next.
Hey!
I told you
the FS does regular bag checks, didn't I?
They don't even know what an egg is.
What an unbelievable bunch.
After school, let's gather at that place.
Phew.
It's really unbelievable, isn't it?
That there's a hidden base
in the school's basement.
Yeah.
We have to remember
the hidden command for the...
direct route from the school building.
It was apparently an underground
military facility during the war
that has since been renovated.
They must have anticipated...
that someone would rise up
against the Perverted Ordinance.
It even seems to be equipped with
a device to scramble GPS signals.
Is this a 3D printer?
It's the latest model.
I started using it right away.
An escape item disguised as an adult toy.
I call it the TAE.
By disguising it as an adult toy,
we can deceive their eyes.
Though it was pretty close this morning.
But if you carry a lot,
won't it look suspicious?
I've already come up with a countermeasure.
Huh?
A Gachapon machine?
Yes, we'll disguise them as that
and leave them all over the island.
With my program, I can track
the location of the perverts.
So if we sense danger,
we can turn the Gachapon machine
and be armed.
People on Seiran Island
don't buy sex toys, after all.
Not a bad idea.
Alright, let's put the plan into action.
PERVERT LAND
Two bows, two claps, one bow.
Two fucks, two tentacles, one bang.
With this, the placement is complete.
What is that?
It's from the original capsule machine.
Oh, an orgasm-button.
Why do we have to be on patrol?
Can't be helped. We're the newbies.
Crap, it's the FS.
Wait. If we run,
it'll just make us more suspicious.
H-Hey.
Let's fool them... with sex.
Sex?
Just pretend.
Ahh... Ah more!
Hey, you should move a little too.
Nothing abnormal.
Ahh!
You can't!
Noo! Ahh!
Ah... Ah... hmm.
They're finally gone.
You okay?
Did you hate it that much?
No...
That's not it.
I...
had my life ruined by my dick.
Huh?
Actually, I have a huge dick.
Eh?
And it's not just a normal huge dick.
It's an exceptionally huge dick
that defies common sense.
Because of that, a long time ago...
"So huge!"
"Is that a horse's dick?"
"Disgusting!"
"There's a limit to everything!"
Ever since then...
I've been terrified of other people
seeing or touching my dick.
Anyway, thanks to you, we got past the FS.
But is it okay?
Abetting a criminal
who violated the ordinance?
It's a bit late for that, isn't it?
Besides,
I understand the feeling
of wanting to do perverted things...
only with someone special.
You're hungry, right?
Huh?
Big brother, a proper human meal.
Both my parents work, you know.
Thanks to that, the housework
has become all my job.
Thanks for the food.
Big brother.
Asa-chan.
It's delicious!
You two used to live here
a long time ago, right?
What were you like?
Neither of us had any friends.
Your sister too?
But she's so cute.
That's because...
Um...
I...
like girls.
Eh?
I got bullied after that came out.
I've kept it a secret ever since.
It's disgusting, right?
I'm sorry for telling you this.
Nanase-san...
I'm sorry for asking
something so hard to talk about.
W-What is this incredibly happy feeling?
I'd have no regrets
if I suffocated to death...
in these boobs right now.
In fact, I'm glad
I was bullied in the past.
From now on, you can think of me
as your big sister.
Jun too, please eat a lot.
Jun?!
I can't tell you two apart
if I just call you Tachibana.
You can just call me Nanase.
Wait, a guy and a girl
who aren't even dating...
It's fine.
You too, Asa-chan.
Asa-chan...
It's no good,
my brain's capacity is overflowing.
My happiness gauge is at max.
Come in.
I should probably get going.
I put tomorrow's breakfast in the fridge.
You even did that.
The TAE, was it?
You're making another one?
This is a hobby.
I've been making my own for a long time.
The recent advancements
in 3D printers are amazing.
So that's how you were able
to make something like that.
It's pretty popular, you know.
MASTER, I THOUGHT MY XXX WOULD MELT
I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO YOUR NEW WORK!!
I WANT TO ORDER 10 MORE.
Ahaha.
Katagiri...
No, Nanase.
Thank you for accepting Asa-chan.
Huh?
Thanks to you,
I got to see my sister's happy smile.
I think it's been since before
our parents died.
That incident...
still haunts her.
Eating delicious food...
and laughing with someone
helps take her mind off things a little.
There's a limit to what
I can do alone as her brother.
Asa-chan is really
important to you, isn't she, Jun?
True.
I want her to be smiling always.
But...
this island has no consideration
for a sexuality like my sister's...
nor does it for people like me
who abhor sex without love.
I can understand bowing down
to the majority for the sake of money.
But does that mean it's okay
to trample on the minority?
I don't want to lose to the peer pressure
that says being perverted is normal.
I will definitely defend my own dignity
and my sister's identity
Maybe there are others.
People on this island
who can't fit in with the perversion.
Nukitashi.
Mmm.
This is the problem, after all.
If only they were bigger.
I've been eating lots of fried chicken
and massaging them, but...
Whoops.
Almost forgot.
PERVERT LAND
I have to have sex
like everyone else, but...
Huh?
Yo, I'm Captain XXX.
Let's XXX together in Never-Never Land
to the sound of the clock!
Huh? M-Me?
Mmm?
Huh?
LOLI PROHIBITED
Oh, my bad.
Get off the ship.
So I'm just a woman
that no one wants after all.
Ah, dicks are so good...
- first thing in the morning!
- Spread your legs!
Get pregnant, now!
Because I haven't had sex...
I'm a bad girl
who's violating the ordinance.
Your thing is so hot.
My inside is so warm.
Why do you marvel so on your own?
This pleasant hole, for myriad things
Therefore, become aesthetically pregnant.
This is too indulgent
for a virgin like me.
I want to have perverted sex like this too.
I wonder what it feels like.
To have a man's dick inside me...
It must be embarrassing.
HIGH SCHOOL HEALTH
AND PHYSICAL EDUCATION
Alright, I need to do some sexercises
so I can have sex too.
Even one finger is a little...
painful.
Like this?
What are you doing?
Oh, Rei-chan, what about lunch?
It's work.
I'm stepping up patrols.
The one we sent to the guillotine
might just be the tip of the iceberg.
That must be tough.
Hey, Rei-chan.
If I were a bad girl...
would you hate me?
Of course not.
No matter what kind of person you are...
I would never hate my childhood friend.
Rei-chan.
Right.
It's not that
I don't want to have sex, but...
I'm fat, so I don't want
anyone to see me naked.
I don't want to have sex
with a girl like this.
I'm sure Hamedori-kun thinks so too.
XXX, hame.
If I had sex like this...
Push! Push! Push!
This wouldn't be perverted sex,
it'd be sumo wrestler sex!
(DOSUKOI IS A CHANT IN SUMO)
If by some chance
they found out I'm a virgin...
I'd have to expose my ugly body
at the guillotine.
Let's sex!
I have to go on a diet after all.
If I use this, I should be able to both
diet and be perverted.
It's such... a genius idea.
DON'T EAT AFTER 10 PM
Dick, hame.
Katagiri-san, I'm a huge fan!
Your famous XXX...
please let me fuck it!
I appreciate the sentiment,
but I'm fully booked with XXX.
I was playing all night yesterday
with a creampie bucket relay.
Please, just this once.
I beg you.
If only I were a mature lady
who could play around like Nanase-chan.
If only I were thin
and sexy XXX like Katagiri-san.
Big brother, the escape program
is complete.
Oh!
As expected of my dear sister.
Then good night.
Alright, with this, we can fight the FS.
Seriously though, what the heck
is a creampie bucket relay?
Perfect timing.
Can you check this with me?
What is that?
A video disc sent by a mysterious person.
It's a video disc.
The XXX reaches deep into the XXX.
My XXX is falling
It's just a porn video.
Wait, isn't the actress's voice strange?
You're right,
she's over-explaining the situation.
No, that's not it.
Slow-motion reverse playback.
To the warriors
who oppose the Perverted Ordinance.
I will give you instructions.
To get a perverted body
like Katagiri-san's...
I'm on a cycling diet!
This is the Climax Bicycle!
Heave... ho... heave... ho...
Ohh!
Sex Sex Sex Fuck Fuck Titty Fucking Sex.
STRIPPING JERK-MATE BANK
You believe that message?
Yeah, it's an instruction
from the one who gave us the base
and even financial support.
If it means we can crush
the Perverted Ordinance,
even if it's the devil...
I'll sell my soul.
Me too.
To become a mature lady like Nanase-chan...
I'll play around at night.
Hmm, that sounds a little different.
Mmm.
Haaah.
So beautiful.
Somehow, it all feels like a lie.
Big sister.
Big sister!
It's hurt.
Help me, big sister.
Takeshi-kun's XXX suddenly got big.
Could it be...
he wants to do perverted things with me?
Help me!
Big sister, you're
an elementary schooler, right?
Takeshi-kun is only four!
It's... it's scary, but...
if I endure it,
maybe I won't be a bad girl anymore.
Big sister.
Ahh!!
Huh?
Did my stomach growl?
That sound just now...
Jun, that scream just now...
Right.
Let's go. This way.
No! Stop it!
Why won't you help me?
That's right.
I'm going to put my XXX in your XXX.
I remember reading that in a picture book.
I don't want to.
I really don't want to do this.
I don't want it to be like this.
My first time...
AHH...
should be a wonderful experience
like in a shoujo manga.
Big sister!
Looks like we made it just in time.
Yes.
Nanase Kakagiri-chan and...
Who is that?
W-What are you guys doing?
Normally, we don't introduce ourselves...
but we'll make an exception for you.
We are the Anti-Copulation Force
We bring down the hammer of justice
on all loveless, perverted sex.
Anti-Copulation...
Force?
Hey, it has been a while
We finally met again
I wonder, have you been doing okay
Just kidding! So happy,
but I'm also blushing
Hey, maybe not this one
maybe not that one too
I fret about the little things I've done
Will you even notice
I tried my very best
to dress up nicely for everyone
Should I be bold and make a move
No guarantee that you will approve
It's all or nothing? I can't do that
Ahhh, I think I have fallen flat
This story that I share with you
Has way too many options
Got to make my mind up and be brave
So the role of heroine is mine to be
It has to be real love
It must be from your love
Cause even I am so in love with you
A cliché story's not the thing for me
And laying plot points, how can that be
Worry, worry, worry, and then fall
Keep worrying and falling
It has to be real love
It must be from your love
Don't forget the promise that we made
I'm just kidding, a sweet lie is okay
Actually, what I want is the real thing
Ahhh... I'm begging, please love me